### Summary

Highly skilled data analyst and Microsoft certified Power BI Data Analyst Associate. Accomplished data modeller with a flair for visualisation. Pro-active team player with strong work ethic and extensive project implementation experience, with polished communication and technical skills. Proficient in establishing good working relationships across all levels of the business to deliver successful outcomes for data projects.

EU citizen, no sponsorship required, located in Amsterdam.

#### Skills

#### Technical

SQL • DAX • Power BI • GitHub • SSRS • Python • R • KNIME • Figma

#### Soft

Project management • Agile delivery • Leadership • Training • Communication • Documentation • Stakeholder management

### Certifications

*PL-300* Microsoft Power BI Data Analyst Associate

### Relevant experience

### Data Analyst | Uinsure

Jun 2023 - Sep 2024

Undertook ad hoc data analysis. Designed, developed and managed Power BI environment. Managed and mentored a junior data analyst and data interns.

- Created reports which covered all aspects of the business **supporting senior and medium-level management with actionable insight**. E.g. in the weekly trading meeting to drive the business' sales decisions and as part of business pitches to acquire new partners for the business
- Built strong relationships with key stakeholders and a good understanding of the household and landlord insurance market
- Provided reports which helped the business spot and develop a variety of process optimisation initiatives, which drove conversion improvements
- Developed reports that provided business monitoring for performance, target adherence indicators, anomaly detection and enabled the business to respond flexibly to changes in both supplier and customer behaviour/demand
- Produced several **reports shared with external partners** to provide them with essential insight. Managed access to the reports and external security for the reports
- Managed and mentored a junior analyst and data interns. This included onboarding, familiarising them with the business and industry, and transfer of knowledge and skills
- Evaluated the accuracy and quality of some of the external data sets used for data enrichment. The analysis resulted in altering the approach to data enrichment to improve quote accuracy
- Created Power BI training materials and delivered Power BI training to stakeholders across several internal departments to increase data literacy and data self-serving/data analysis in the business
- Awarded 'Above and Beyond' Business Values Award in August 2023

# Junior Data Analyst | Uinsure

Nov 2022 - Jun 2023

Completed data projects and managed the Power BI environment.

- **Developed first company-wide reports** capturing aspects of the business that had never been exposed before
- The reports covered all areas of the insurance leads' journey. This **offered the senior and medium-level management insight needed to start optimising the customer journey** in a data-driven way



#### Data Science Intern | Uinsure

Jul 2022 - Sep 2022

Developed reports as the first data hire in the company. Gathered requirements from the stakeholders and delivered a complete product.

• Performed data cleaning, pre-processing and data modelling. Created a complex data model with multiple fact and dimension tables. Hired permanently as a part of the newly created Data Team

### **Testing Specialist | Bluecrest Wellness**

Aug 2020 - Dec 2021

Collected data and assisted with COVID-19 tests for the Office of National Statistics (ONS) COVID-19 Infection Survey.

• Independently interviewed the participants to gather accurate and complete data

#### Education

#### **MSc Data Science | University of Sheffield**

Sep 2020 - Sep 2022

- 1st Class Hons.
- Thesis: Analysis of profile variations of dating app users and their dating preferences. Performed kmeans clustering algorithm to group real dating app users and analysed the messaging behaviour between the groups
- Subjects: data mining (in KNIME), data analysis (in R), database design, data visualisation (in R), BI

## BSc (Hons) Psychology with Clinical Psychology | University of Lincoln Sep 2016 - Sep 2019

- 2.1 Upper Second Class Hons.
- Thesis: The effect of cognitive load and anxiety on forming the first impression of trustworthiness
- Subjects: research skills (in SPSS), psychopharmacology, clinical psychology, abnormal psychology
- Awarded 'Lincoln Award' for completing extracurricular courses. Volunteered at off-campus English classes

### A-levels | Adam Mickiewicz 6th Upper Secondary School

Sep 2013 - May 2016

• Obtained Polish equivalent of A-levels in: Mathematics, English, Biology and Polish

# Languages

- English (fluent)
- Polish (fluent)
- Dutch (A1.1)

#### Interests

- · board games collector
- reading
- cooking
- rowing